Narrator: Chris
Chris: I like cooking alone. I don’t like having other people in the kitchen.
But I like eating with friends, especially when I’m out. I don’t like being alone in a restaurant.
Narrator: Sarah
Sarah: I don’t like travelling alone – I prefer going on holiday with friends.
But they need to be the right friends!
Narrator: Mike
Mike: I like shopping with friends.
When I go alone I usually buy things that look horrible on me.
I need a second opinion!
Narrator: Greta
Greta: I love dancing alone at home to really old music from the 70s, like Abba.
But I never dance with other people at parties because I know I’m a terrible dancer.
Narrator: Veronica
Veronica: I like watching films with friends. When the film finishes, we can talk about it,
and I like having someone with me so we can be happy or frightened together!
Narrator: Becca
Becca: I like running alone. It helps me to concentrate, and it’s very peaceful!
But I prefer going for walks with other people because I like walking and talking.
Narrator: Andy
Andy: I like driving alone.
I love listening to my favourite music in the car and singing very loudly –
but with the windows closed of course!